[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does IC stand for in a computer?", "correct_answer": "Integrated Circuit", "incorrect_answers": ["Integrated Chip", "InterChip", "InterCircuit"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What part of any animal is absolutely forbidden for consumption by Jewish laws?", "correct_answer": "Blood", "incorrect_answers": ["Head", "Heart", "Internal organs"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "He was the voice of Dr. Adams on the radio version of Gunsmoke and most notably he played the role of Floyd the Barber on The Andy Griffith Show.", "correct_answer": "Howard McNear", "incorrect_answers": ["Frank Goshin", "Milburn Stone", "Zebulah Geer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the occupation of TV personality Harry Volkman?", "correct_answer": "TV weatherman", "incorrect_answers": ["TV variety show host", "TV news caster", "TV game show host"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the shape of the Italian Peninsula?", "correct_answer": "Boot", "incorrect_answers": ["Skull", "Dog", "Hand"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "People with depression usually know they are depressed.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Alabama Hills is a desert location used in many movies.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which term does not belong with the others?", "correct_answer": "Poaching", "incorrect_answers": ["Pot Roasting", "Braising", "Stewing"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Aliens, which two marines were discovered to still be alive after the escape from the initial fire fight?", "correct_answer": "Sarge and Dietrich", "incorrect_answers": ["Spiff and Simon", "Dietrich and Drake", "Crowe and Frost"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Approximately how long is the Martian solar day?", "correct_answer": "24 hours 39 minutes", "incorrect_answers": ["48 hours 30 minutes", "12 hours 35 minutes", "15 hours"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the first name of the comedian, who in 1999 became host of The Daily Show?", "correct_answer": "Jon", "incorrect_answers": ["Stu", "Lou", "Ray"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The town of Pilsen, famous for the production of beer, is situated in western Bohemia, in the Czech Republic. It became a town in 1295 when it received its civic charter from which ruler?", "correct_answer": "King Wenceslaus II", "incorrect_answers": ["Jan Hus", "Napoleon", "Rudolf II"]}]